yo yo this is quick today quick stream
guys quick stream hmm
wait for all I should go at least put it
on on Twitter yeah well we'll do it with
the Subaru harness is live nick is alive
on the site right now no wait what
I don't have Wi-Fi or something Oh yo yo
we live we learn Subaru varnas going
live wait hang on I got to find our
Channel I got to find our channel I'm on
Twitter what's up we got an announcement
for everybody here in a minute in a
minute
youtube.com he's alive
hey come on there's a lot I know I just
push it to the uh-oh no push is what
side yeah yeah
alright alright alright alright alright
alright
when's the test jumper coming oh no test
Jarek but if you want to see the new one
logger I can show you that check it out
I wrote this beautiful UI myself this is
like engaged it's like Explorer of it
fast
alright I do we are we good
live chat welcome to live chat oh yeah
you think July go again why I worked I
worked hard on this UI that's the speed
of the car so then like you can see this
is like you I you know yo yo yo alright
hello world it's a short announcement
today just short announcement think like
too short
I blocked Twitter in my Etsy host file
because otherwise I just go on Twitter
all that how am i doing today we're
doing good today
what do it good today alright I don't
really know there's not too much to say
in live streams this is gonna be mad
short but um so this is uh this is open
pilot here if you go down to supported
cars we already support the Subaru
Crosstrek and Impreza we also have a
pull request which means we're gonna get
support pretty soon for the Subaru
Legacy and the Subaru Outback no
promises on those but if you have a
cross tracker and present today and you
buy we're gonna refresh this webpage in
a little bit but first we're gonna go
for a walk
these are Subaru harnesses they attach
to your black panda in your harness so
this is just the standard , 28 pin
connector and that's your pass through
four Subaru neither of these connectors
is 3d printed they're both real
connectors why nobody's gonna come to
the stream today we didn't announce it
we didn't plan anything but Subaru do
you see what this says it says ready to
ship so that's just because it's ready
to ship do you have any comments on the
on the Subaru harness oh oh there's all
secrets Oh secrets Wow
wow there's so much so many leaks in
here no no nope we can't have any leaks
does anyone does anyone have any
comments on the Subaru harness eyesight
required yeah it should work with all
cars with eyesight all right oh no I'm
not you they can't see your screen don't
worry Wow wow this is this is this is
leaked said Julia wow there's so many
leaks going on and there's leaks on this
ticket what is that thick you know it's
a tiny leak is there any leaks here
where leaks rinche weeks all right
that's it for leaks let's we'll just
wait till it goes live right now but
with the Subaru horn
Subaru is it live yet it's not live yet
but just so you know we make the
development vehicle this is like that
stream when Elon announced the model y
and nobody really cared it's like that
but we're announcing the Subaru harness
let me go get a Subaru harness so I can
hold it up every time I say Subaru
harness I can't show you oh
leaks no no no we're walking down here
so so nobody can see any leaks no leaks
no leaks no leaks no we will show you
the datacenter you know I love showing
off the datacenter wow it's beautiful
it's so big we did can't leak to you the
door code well they're gonna be
analyzing those leaks for a long time
yeah oh you wants to print a farm we
gotta go look at printer farm this is a
Subaru harness print farm Civic
Oh Oh is those FCI not launched yet but
that's an FCA connector walk so don't
worry you didn't miss anything we're
just launching the Subaru harness today
we have a black band around our harness
thingy that I can plug it into so this
will be mounted inside your Tsuru it's
the same one that goes in the Civic in
the Toyota Subaru harness if you by
Subaru harness for $400 yeah one only
half only half the FCA is this alone
yeah look at that look at how satisfying
this Joe anything to say about the
Subaru harness yeah with this is what
we're showing I haven't even seen this
oh look at that Wow it's like is it nice
nice plastic huh yeah okay are these the
real we didn't print these no no we're
together right don't plug it in like
that when you get it it intercepts your
Subaru it should work with all new
Subarus with eyesight I believe and you
see this it passes through five of the
wires the Subaru harnesses back do we
have the old Subaru harnesses around to
show them now it was bad it was bad we
sold three of them so I'm hoping Gilly
I'm acknowledging your message by a
harness for your Subaru today when it's
common doing an IPO that's a
forward-looking statement I'm not
allowed to say that no you can hack your
own Subaru with the Subaru harness buy
it today prevent low speed lockout oh
I'm excited about the smart TSU
intercept you're gonna sell them what is
it going live alright why don't we go
live to our sales team and we ask when
they're going live
Subaru harness : life super harness is
almost like we got we got 81 people here
they're very excited for Subaru harness
it's gonna be a 20-minute yeah hey you
know do you have any comments when the
Subaru horn is good any comments on the
Subaru harness it's finally time whoa
whoa whoa no torquing acceptors Petar
see how thank you for buying one you
make it worth it for us you're just
gonna drop down I think we're adding
reading uh just crosstrack and uh yeah
cool and that sorry is it on the leg
harness nice nice Subaru now officially
supported by comma a we're doing FCA
soon to sew the harness you know harness
technology Oh exclusive leaks for come a
prime subscribers okay everybody else
cover your ears wait wait we actually
have an exclusive league for come over
I'm subscribers we actually have one
can we easily show them take pic they
ask for leaks for common prime
subscribers yeah yo check this out look
at the pictures it's taken pictures
right now alright so this is the
front-facing camera and this is y'all
look at me it's me guys look we did it
yeah so that's an exclusive that's gonna
be a comma prime exclusive feature
you're gonna be able to take a picture
with your car make sure to sign up for
come from before we rate the prices yeah
yeah gamma prime prime just incredible
do you intentionally stream on data to
minimize leaks no not streaming a data
eric moraga whoa finally something cool
baa what what we'll celebrate with it
when the Subaru harness goes live I
don't know what that is look a
skateboard ssh become a prime now with
camera
wait youtube showed you an ad what am i
getting new revenue for that i don't
think so the leak I think we cover like
50 something cars yeah yeah so just so
if you already bought a harness for some
reason um you'll be able to buy just
this table for 50 bucks but if you buy a
harness it includes the harness it
includes the common power v2 it includes
the Black Panda yeah we'll buy Google
man no you know what we'll buy like one
of those car companies one of those
American car companies when they don't
get bailed out we'll bottle that's right
and we'll fire everybody and replace
them with robots
so saya any robot any roadmap for flex
right cars no you are out of luck buy a
cheaper car bro trade in your car you
know when you go to a dealership you can
trade in a car and they'll actually give
you money if the trade-in value of
hire the new car don't buy GM um if I
buy Faraday future yeah bloated
I'm fingerprinting to point out yeah
we're working on it we're working on it
what was the unlocker stuff is just
something that's what I've been working
on this week it's actually already like
if you go and open pilot tools and you
look in Nui how's the sound division
doing sound division is killing it we
love the new sound clarity uh-oh I don't
know about that one oh yeah I'm sorry
you bought a weird car if you trade it
in your car you'd ask for money well I
don't know how to uh leaks all right
let's see this is my new auger Dearing
controls for
and you Pam but their their $50 black
panda , power v2 includes the correct
wire for your Subaru USBC cable Ethernet
cable and that's what your yun looks
like mounted well these aren't leaks
this won't live a while ago you want to
see leaks these are the websites that I
block um is it lagging he's a quality
bad oh wow wow it's real potato quality
that's bad that's low-quality crap Queen
increase the quality
wow that's I don't know man that's bad
but ya know Subarus gonna go live any
minute now
we'll just sit here we'll just sit here
I'll wait with you guys while suber goes
live no I'm on my Wi-Fi I don't I don't
get it
Oh yo you know what I got in the mail
today but I don't have it my air pons
air pod pro that was no leaks on the
board the second I'm paranoid about
leaks Oh Oh guys guys it's live it's
live right now you can pick your Subaru
Crosstrek or your Stuber Oh impress out
and you can add to cart' you know what
this guy's a known hater you know what
happens to known haters hide user on
this channel perfect uh-oh the accordi
PS oh you want to show me according PS
[Music]
yeah so so Subaru right they're only
three ninety-nine that's a good price
you're good bro I like you I'll give you
a harness for 399 super easy just buy it
right now I'm just gonna check quickly
to see if anybody's buying it you know
what if we've sold if we sell at least
if we sell three of them in the next two
minutes we're gonna show you guys the
accordi PS but if we don't sell three of
them we're not showing your decoy TPS
anyone buy any yet come on bye bye bye
no one's bought any yet if our harness
is a fantastic product thank you
where's nougat cosmos leagues leagues
all right let's go and just go ahead and
see what the live live leaking situation
is Subaru people yeah come on you know
you want to see the accordion you got it
you got a buy no super people buy
anything
Oh Subaru
oh so quick all the leaks got covered up
the leaks are gone oh you didn't get any
leaks people might be buying a Subaru um
if you're going out and buying a Subaru
may I recommend it to Lyoto Corolla but
if you're
the situation will you already have a
Subaru come on we go we got we gotta
sell a few of these zero sold so far but
only 90 viewers I know I know I know
because we didn't do any real press for
this because it's like you know it's
low-quality crap you got an exclusive ,
prime leak yeah take picture bros mah by
subaru but also another thing if you
don't have a harness for your car you
should get a harness even if you don't
have a Subaru um
Oh Bugsy I mean if yours has the same
pin outs as ours and you're using the
same harness absolutely keeps telling
him we're just we're not making a lot of
money on these cables that's why they've
been debunked glad you enjoyed the
medium article 2020 Corolla hybrid I
think we fixed that oh sorry we fixed
that in the secret good version of open
pilot don't fix it
it's up what if you buy a hundred two
weeks from now if you actually want to
buy we have we have bulk discounts um
we've gotten a few orders in the last
couple weeks of 10 Yuans
and we offer decent discounts for buying
ten so you can just reach out supporter
comment I have you're serious about
buying in large quantities if you're
buying a hundred will give you a
phenomenal price yeah
oh yeah zero six six I think I think let
me just double check but I think zero
six six is gonna support the the Corolla
hybrid yes alright alright you want to
see some more leaks I'll show you some
more than leaks leaks thanks walk so
alright guys I'm glad to have you all
here with me
but unfortunately uh I don't think
anyone uh yep no people and he's super
honest I really does anyone actually
have a sugru or is it just trolls oh
crap that was a leak
oh we leaked that oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
Jay Young has done a great job we're
super happy no trucks no how many
versions before zero seven well that's
that so that's too much of a leak no I
think the issue is that nobody actually
has a Subaru if you buy if you buy your
stuff today well I promise we'll support
your uh your Corolla hybrid by the time
against their depends you know like I
know some like I know some like like
people who have Subarus but they're like
Subarus from 1992 I don't know anybody
who buys a new burro
so I'm just I'm just okay so we sold
exactly zero Subaru harnesses so guess
why uh you don't get you don't get to
see the uh yeah if you buy me a super
exactly exactly
oh you have a nineteen Forester all
right let's the point that soon I think
I think of all the cars have it now you
don't have a neon yeah yo okay I'll show
you guys I'll show you get yeah yeah
we're working on the Outback but we got
we gotta merge that I know I know
ten sales ten sales will be great you
mean ten young sales that'd be
phenomenal who'd be so happy with Kenny
on sales but I did leak how much money
we made this but we're rich boys
Subaru's torque seems pretty good yes
super or nice cars if you get over the
fact of our supers but I don't mean to
discourage anybody with the Subaru if
you guys were if you guys were all you
know buying up this harness really fast
I'd be like man you guys are all great I
love Subaru people but well nobody buys
anything well you know how do how do I
handle em how am I supposed to feel um
but I believe in you Subaru people I
know that maybe you take your time to me
to make a decision
I'm not running ads I don't know if
there are ads if you buy a Subaru
harness right now will I make the Kia oh
they found out one yeah yeah we're
working on that you a Kia kiyow kiyow
Hyundai are the same car right superhot
is canceled out now when I cancel it
anymore
okay we know we're doing we're doing the
q1 as well
all right what other what other car
ports we want buy a Subaru one right now
and what we'll do the key light will do
it even if you don't buy Subaru harness
but somebody's coming refresh on the
sales page nope nope nobody nobody buys
Subaru harnesses but if you're excited
about that , prime leak make sure to
find kama prime go in your comment app
is very convenient and easy it could
somebody please buy us a new harness
Great Wall SUVs I don't know about that
nope we're just gonna we're just going
to leave this stream where absolutely uh
you know last time we did the super
harness we sold three how many people
have a Subaru that open pilot
I can't believe nobody bought them
either this is the website broken Subaru
harnesses are a great deal okay they're
only 399 for your Subaru I mean it makes
your Subaru like like way better you
know those things you forget you have a
Subaru oh because you already all have
harnesses okay oh I think we can check
the stats yeah bring that up once I'm
fingerprinted vehicles relative let's
say 30
oh you can't process payments what Oh
let me show to work um almost you guys
are early adopters who already bought
all right cool I know we're not going 30
months ago although 30 days ago I will
update let's see oh oh oh we see you
here
here we go so our most popular car of
course is the toyota prius followed by
nun civics see RVs vaults city civics
Corollas Accords Corollas rap fours
Accords rap fours
Honda's Odysseys Camrys rap force
Accords CRV is Camrys we hyundai oh oh
there we go
15 Subaru Impreza limited
there we go that's Subaru I think
they're all upstream cars yeah Wow three
likes on the three likes on the on the
Subaru and one of them's our car to help
your parents have a Subaru
I add more add more yeah yeah yeah what
will it more but this isn't encouraging
this isn't encouraging for Subarus who
set up I acknowledge them they were
gonna buy one can you get a tutorial
yeah if you search for open pilot
carport and do a medium post I did all
these leaks for you I won't be pretty
bought a harness alright alright alright
well you can't process payment I don't
know what there's no new hardware you
guys got the new hardware the new
hardware already came out it's called
the car harness go check it out it's not
a pin post on Twitter
you'll have to wait till 2020 I knew we
all know I don't know about that yo if
you guys want to see how many lay echoes
we have to continue making yawns Gilly
come on and cold quick let's if this
dream gets to the 30 minute mark and not
even a single sugru harnason soul I'm
just gonna I'm gonna sit at my desk and
I'm gonna go get ice cream actually
that's what I'm gonna do and you know
what if one is sold I'm gonna go get ice
cream too but the difference is that if
one gets sold it's gonna be celebration
ice cream and if none get sold its gonna
be feel better ice cream guys Legos are
the future toppings where's no toppings
now we're not getting toppings we're
going to a shukshin scoops no no no
short lestrade that's it okay okay okay
at least we got seven likes on the on
the Subaru harness no no no no we're
gonna eat a moderate amount of ice cream
we're gonna eat in moderation Wow
well you know what I was thinking about
doing a stream for the FCI harness but
now there's no FCI harness stream and
you know why the FCA people the FCA
people can blame the Subaru people for
not buying any Oh nonono shippers /
shippers / you know why shippers / guys
because they're no longer giving us any
free cloud money when they gave us lots
of free cloud money we ran chipper and
then the free cloud money runs out and
then the shipper runs out cuz shipper
didn't you know make any money but
apparently Subaru harnesses don't make
any money either oh no oh yeah you know
about that is that Arduino Uno that's
what I'm talking about yeah I don't know
I don't feel like streaming on Twitch
anymore this is a stream that you get if
you want if you want to stream this is
the stream you get 30 more seconds of
stream come on come on buy a super
check them an Apple watch
quick Gilly get in I'm just gonna show
you guys the accordi PS I'm gonna show
you more great leaks but nope nobody
blows horn all right we'll see all you
later thank you for joining me for the
stream have a nice evening and today we
learned the truth that there are no
people out there who actually own a
Subaru just people who say that they do
bye bye